There's a new kid on the protocol block.
No, not the 90s boy band.
MCP-S
Verifiable runtime evidence for MCP calls.
MCP gives agents a standard way to connect to tools,
source control, databases, internal docs, calendars,
payment APIs, and the systems developers already use.
That is why developers like it.
Instead of one-off glue for every tool and every host,
MCP gives us reusable integrations with a common shape.
Host, client, server, tool.
But that call path is also a boundary.
Once an agent asks a tool to do something sensitive,
we need evidence about identity, integrity,
freshness, replay, and response binding.
Take a payment request.
The agent sends pay invoice 1042.
If that call can be copied, replayed or changed,
one trusted action can become two bad ones.
MCP-S adds verifiable runtime evidence
around those MCP calls.
A request can carry a signature, a nonce,
an expiry, authorization context, and a request hash.
The response can be bound back with its own hash.
The point is not magic security.
The point is evidence that a verifier
can check while the system is running.
For enterprise deployments, signing keys
can stay in Google Cloud KMS.
MCP-S asks KMS to sign.
The private key is not exported.
MCP-S receives signatures, not raw key material.
The payoff is operational and testable.
Valid requests are accepted, tampered requests are rejected,
replays are rejected, and bad response bindings are rejected.
Try MCP-S at github.com/matssun/mcps.